(Sheldon:)...of a specific object or organism.
(Sheldon:)Mimesis.
(Leonard:)What the hell are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)I'm attempting
to communicate with you...
(Sheldon:)...without my meaning becoming
apparent to those around you.
(Sheldon:)Let me try again.
(Sheldon:)Have the indigenous fauna
accepted you as one of their own?
(Sheldon:)Nudge, nudge, wink, wink.
(Leonard:)Oh, I guess so.
(Sheldon:)Good. Oh, FYI,
after I eat my sandwich...
(Sheldon:)...I'm taking Koothrappali's Patang kite
out for a test run.
Would you get your Delta Wing Raptor
and join me?
I don't wanna fly kites, Sheldon.
Come on, we're watching football here.
(Sheldon:)I can see that.
I was providing you with an alternative.
(Sheldon:)A courtesy I was never offered
in similar circumstances.
(Leonard:)Oh, look at that. The Oklahoma coach
has thrown down a red flag...
(Leonard:)...indicating he's challenging
the ruling on the field.